Shrek's Thrilling Tales is a comedy, family, animation film directed by None.
SHREK'S THRILLING TALES is the ultimate Halloween
DVD compilation for your family.
Shrek's Thrilling Tales review Featuring the scariest, ugliest, and funniest
characters from DreamWorks Animation's successful SHREK and MONSTERS VS.
ALIENS franchises.
DVD includes 'The Pig who Cried (Were)Wolf' and 'The Ghost of Lord Farquaad' from
the Shrek movies, and 'Night of the Living Carrots' from Monsters vs.
Aliens, featuring B.O.B.
Shrek (voice), played by Mike Myers.
Donkey (voice), played by Eddie Murphy.
Princess Fiona (voice), played by Cameron Diaz.
Dr. Cockroach Ph.D. (voice), played by Hugh Laurie.
B.O.B. (voice), played by Seth Rogen.
Gingerbread Man (voice), played by Conrad Vernon.
Shrek is an American media franchise of DreamWorks Animation.
Loosely based on William Steig's 1990 picture book Shrek!, the series primarily focuses on Shrek, a bad-tempered but good-hearted ogre, who begrudgingly
accepts a quest to rescue a princess, resulting in him finding friends and going on many subsequent adventures in a fairy tale world.
The franchise includes four animated films: Shrek (2001), Shrek 2 (2004), Shrek the Third (2007), and Shrek
Forever After (2010), with a fifth film, Shrek 5, currently in production for a June 2027 release.
A short 4-D film, Shrek 4-D, which originally was a
theme park ride, was released in 2003.
Two television specials, the Christmas television special Shrek the Halls (2007) and the
Halloween television special Scared Shrekless (2010), have also been produced.
Two spin-off films were made centered around the character Puss in Boots:
2011's Puss in Boots and its sequel, 2022's The Last Wish.
Additionally, a stage musical adaptation was created and played
on Broadway for more than a year (2008–2010).
In May 2010, The New York Times described the principal Shrek characters as "brilliantly realized" and said "nearly a decade after the first Shrek film they remain as vital and engaging fusions of image, personality, and voice as any characters in the
history of animation." The series was a financial success, becoming the 18th highest-grossing film franchise of all time, the second highest-grossing animated franchise, as well one of the highest-grossing media franchises of all time.
The film explores themes of candy, halloween, swamp, zombie, trick or treat.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.